Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: New American Library, Editorial/Author Files
  - Angkor, general information, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 2062)
  - Aristophanes, general information, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2063)
  - Arthur, Burt, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2064)
  - Asbell, Bernard, "The Death of F.D.R.,", 1960-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2065)
  - Asimov, Isaac, "The Chemicals of Life,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2066)
  - Asimov, Isaac, "The Human Body and the Human Brain,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2067)
  - Asimov, Isaac, five volumes on science, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2068)
  - Aswell, James (Mrs.), general correspondence, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 2069)
  - Atlas, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2070)
  - Aurelius, Marcus, "Meditations,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2071)
  - Austen, Jane, "Pride and Prejudice,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2072)
  - Austen, Jane, "Sense and Sensibility,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2073)
  - Austin, Alex, "Working Wife,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2074)
  - Australia, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2075)
  - Azuela, Manuel, "The Underdogs,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2076)
  - Babel, Isaac, "Lyubka the Cossack and Other Stories,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2077)
  - Baines, Keith, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2078)
  - Bakeless, John, "Journals of Lewis and Clark,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2079)
  - Ballard, James, "Chronopolis,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2080)
  - Ballinger, Bill, general correspondence, 1951-1959 (Box 78, Folder 2081)
  - Ballinger, Bill, "Formula #2 for Murder,", 1958 (Box 78, Folder 2082)
  - Ballinger, Bill, untitled novel, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 2083)
  - Balzac, Honore de, "Le Peau de Chagrin,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2084)
  - Banks, Polan, "The Sleeping Woman," "Maharajah,", 1960-1968 (Box 78, Folder 2085)
  - Barley, Rex, "How to Handle Your Own Public Relations,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2086)
  - Barnet, Sylvan, "Genius of the Early English Theater,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2087)
  - Barnett, Lincoln, literary projects company, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2088)
  - Bassett, James, "Go in Harm's Way,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2089)
  - Bates, H.E., "A Breath of French Air,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2090)
  - Bemelmans, Ludwig, "Are You Hungry Are You Cold,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2091)
  - Benjamin, Claude, "The Skin Game,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2092)
  - Bentley, Eric, "Genius of the Italian Theater,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2093)
  - Berlin, Isaiah, "The Hedgehog and the Fox,", 1956-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2094)
  - Bermel, Albert, "The Genius of the French Theater,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2095)
  - Berry, John, "The Assassin,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2096)
  - Bester, Alfred, "All Possible Worlds,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2097)
  - Bettman Archive, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2098)
  - Bezzarides, A..I., "Coast Country,", 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2099)
  - Bierce, Ambrose, "In the Midst of Life and Other Tales,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2100)
  - Bishop, Paul Byron, untitled, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2101)
  - Blacker, Irwin R., "The Kilroy Gambit,", 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2102)
  - Blankfort, Michael, "Goodbye I Guess,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2103)
  - Blankfort, Michael, "Tower of Fire,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2104)
  - Blau, Joseph, L., "The Story of Jewish Philosophy,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2105)
  - Bligh, William, "The Mutiny on Board H.M.S. Bounty,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2106)
  - Bly, Robert, "The Story of Gosta Berling,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2107)
  - Bobula, Ida, "Hungarian Short Stories", undated (Box 78, Folder 2108)
  - Bowra, C.M., "Primitive Song,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2109)
  - Brogan, D.W., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2110)
  - Brossard, Chandler, "The Girls in Rome,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2111)
  - Brown, Bill, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2112)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "Angel!,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2113)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "The Exotic,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2114)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "Murder Wears a Mantilla,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2115)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], mystery series, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2116)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], 'The Sad-Eyed Seductress,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2117)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "The Stripper,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2118)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "The Tigress,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2119)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], TV project, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 2120)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "The Unorthodox Corpse,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2121)
  - Brown, Carter [pseudonym for Alan Yates], "Zelda,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2122)
  - Brown, William, "Stone the American Embassy,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2123)
  - Brustein, Robert, "Genius of the American Theater,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2124)
  - Burma, John, "Penitentes,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2125)
  - Burns, Walter Noble, "The Saga of Billy the Kid,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2126)
  - Burtt, Edwin A.., "Teachings of the Compassionate Buddha,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2127)
  - Burwell, Basil, "The Unfinished Man,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2128)
  - Butterworth, William, "Circus on the Beach,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2129)
  - Butterworth, William, "The Man Behind the Door,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2130)
  - Butterworth, William, "Where We Go From Here,", 1959-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2131)
  - Cable, George Washington, "Old Creole Days,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2132)
  - Caillou, Alan, "Field of Women,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2133)
  - Caillou, Alan, "The Plotters,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2134)
  - Caillou, Alan, "Rampage,", 1960-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2135)
  - Caillou, Alan, "The Walls of Jolo,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2136)
  - Calder, Ritchie, "After the Seventh Day,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2137)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2138)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Claudette Inglish,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2139)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Close to Home,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2140)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Georgia Boy,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2141)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "God's Little Acre,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2142)
  - Caldwell, Erskine (Caldwell, Virginia), "Honorary Degree,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2143)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Jenny By Nature,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2144)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Men and Women,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2145)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Tobacco Road" (no date), undated (Box 78, Folder 2146)
  - Calsoyas, C.D., "Reading, Intoning, and Comprehending Russian,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2147)
  - Campbell, Robert Wright, "Montgomery Park,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2148)
  - Carrington, Richard, "A Million Years of Man,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2149)
  - Carrington, Richard, "The Story of Our Earth,", 1960-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2150)
  - Cather, Willa, "Troll Garden,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2151)
  - Celliers, Peter J., guidebook, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2152)
  - Chai, Ch'u, and Winberg Chai, "The Changing Society of China,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2153)
  - Chai, Ch'u, and Winberg Chai, "A Treasury of Chinese Literature,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2154)
  - Chambers, Whitman, "69 Libido Drive,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2155)
  - Chandler, David, "The Glass Totem,", 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2156)
  - Chandler, David, "O'Malley's Nuns,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2157)
  - Chang, Diana, "Didi,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2158)
  - Chase, Borden, "Ataturk,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2159)
  - Chase, Richard, "American Folk Songs,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2160)
  - Chateaubriand, Francois Rene de, "Atala and Rene," 1961, undated (Box 78, Folder 2160.A)
  - Chaucer, "The Canterbury Tales,", 1954-1959 (Box 78, Folder 2161)
  - Cheever, John, "Short Stories,", 1957-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2162)
  - Chesser, Eustace, "Love Without Fear,", 1960-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2163)
  - Christman, Henry M., civil war book, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2164)
  - Clark, Manning, "A History of Australia,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2165)
  - Clark, Walter van Tilburg, "The Track of the Cat,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2166)
  - Clayre, Alastair, "The Window,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2167)
  - Cleator, P.E., "Lost Languages,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2168)
  - Cobb, Walter J., language laboratory tape project, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2169)
  - Coleman, James A.., "Origin of the Universe,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2170)
  - Coleman, James A.., "Relativity For the Layman,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2171)
  - Colette, "The Other One,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2172)
  - Collins, Carvel, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2173)
  - Conant, James, "On Understanding Science,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2174)
  - Conrad, Joseph, "Heart of Darkness," "The Secret Sharer,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2175)
  - Conrad, Joseph, "Lord Jim,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2176)
  - Conton, William, "The African,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2177)
  - Converse, Jane, "Alias Miss Saunders, R.N.,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2178)
  - Converse, Jane, "Emergency Nurse,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2179)
  - Converse, Jane, "Second Chance Nurse,", 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 2180)
  - Cooper, James Fenimore, "The Pathfinder,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2181)
  - Cornwall, I.W., "Natural Environment and Archaeology,", 1960 (Box 78, Folder 2182)
  - Corwin, Norman, general correspondence (no date), undated (Box 78, Folder 2183)
  - Costantino, Helen, "How to Know French Antiques,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2184)
  - Cottrell, Leonard, "Anvil of Civilization,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2185)
  - Courlander, Harold, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2186)
  - Cowan, William W., "Toward the Liberally Educated Executive,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2187)
  - Cox, William, "Comanche Moon,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2188)
  - Cox, William, "The Outlawed,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2189)
  - Coyle, David, "The United Nations,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2190)
  - Coyle, David, "The U.S. Political System and How It Works,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2191)
  - Craig, Gordon, lectures project, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2192)
  - Crevecoeur, St. John de, "Sketches of Eighteenth Century America,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2193)
  - crime book, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2194)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus, "George Washington: Man and Monument,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2195)
  - Danielou, Jean, "The Dead Sea Scrols and Primitive Christianity" (no date), undated (Box 78, Folder 2196)
  - Daniels, John S., "The Gunfighters,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2197)
  - Danielsson, Bengt, "The True Story of the Bounty,", 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 2198)
  - David, Alfred, and Mary Elizabeth David, "Anthology of Fairy Tales,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2199)
  - Davidson-Houston, J.V., "Russia and China,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2200)
  - Davis, Gwen, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2201)
  - Davis, Russell F., "I Love You, Mary Fatt,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2202)
  - Dawson, Christopher, "The Dynamics of World History,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2203)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, "The Nature of the Non-Western World,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2204)
  - Dennis, Patrick, "Little Me: The Memoirs of Belle Pointrine,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2205)
  - DeVries, Peter, "Through the Fields of Clover,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2206)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Latitude Eighteen,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2207)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Night of the Tiger,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2208)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Twilight of Honor,", 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2209)
  - Dickens, Charles, "Oliver Twist,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2210)
  - Dickinson, Emily, "Poems,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2211)
  - Dickinson, Patric, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2212)
  - Dimont, Max, "Jews, Jehovah, and History,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2213)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, "Coningsby,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2214)
  - Doctorow, E.L., "Welcome to Hard Times,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2215)
  - Dolphin, Vernon, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2216)
  - Donahue, Jack, "Someone to Hate,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2217)
  - Dooley, Thomas A.., "Before I Sleep,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2218)
  - Dooley, Thomas A.., "Deliver Us From Evil,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2219)
  - Dooley, Thomas A.., "Edge of Tomorrow,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2220)
  - Dooley, Thomas A.., "The Night They Burned the Mountain,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2221)
  - Dostoyevsky, Fyodor, "Notes From Underground,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2222)
  - Dostoyevsky, Fyodor, "The Possessed,", 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2223)
  - Douglas, Shane, general correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2224)
  - Douglas, Shane, "Air Surgeon,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2225)
  - Douglas, Shane, "The Mercy Heroes,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2226)
  - Downs, Robert B., "Books That Changed the World,", 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 2227)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, "Sister Carrie,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2228)
  - Dresner, Samuel, "Conservative Judaism Magazine,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2229)
  - Dudley, Donald R., "Tacitus,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2230)
  - Duerrenmatt, ______, "The Quarry,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2231)
  - Duncan, Tom, "Big River, Big Man,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2232)
  - Dundee, Robert [pseud. Robert Kirsch], "Inferno,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2233)
  - Dundee, Robert [pseud. Robert Kirsch], "Pandora's Box,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2234)
  - Dundee, Robert [pseud. Robert Kirsch], "The Wife Traders,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2235)
  - Dunn, Harold, children's boners, 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2236)
  - Dunn, Harold, "Those Crazy Mized-Up Kids,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2237)
  - Dunn, L.C., "Heredity, Race, and Society,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2238)
  - Du Pont, Gene, "The Twenty-Year Man,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2239)
  - Dwiggins, Don, "The S.O.Bees,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2240)
  - Eberstadt, Frederick, "The Pleasure Seekers,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2241)
  - Edelman, Maurice, "Minister of State,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2242)
  - Eliot, George, "Adam Bede,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2243)
  - Ellis, George, "A Man Called Jones,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2244)
  - Endore, Guy, "Marquis de Sade,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2245)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "The Scattered Seed,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2246)
  - Erasmus, Desiderius, "In Praise of Folly,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2247)
  - Escher, Franklin, "A Brief History of the U.S.,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2248)
  - Esslin, Martin, "Genius of the German Theater,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2249)
  - Eunson, Robert, "West Wind Year,", 1959-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2250)
  - Evans, Frederick, "The Gentle Sin,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2251)
  - Fadiman, William, "Top-Off,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2252)
  - Fairservis, Jr., Walter A.., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2253)
  - Fairservis, Walter, "Ancient Kingdom of the Nile,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2254)
  - Fairservis, Walter, "Origins of Oriental Civilization,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2255)
  - Falconer, Haven, "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, Inc.,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2256)
  - Farrar, Larston D., "The Sins of Sandra Shaw,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2257)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2258)
  - Feiffer, Jules, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2259)
  - Feldman, George, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2260)
  - Fellows, Otis, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2261)
  - Fenton, Charles A., "The Apprenticeship of Ernest,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2262)
  - Fernandez-Flores, Dario, "I Am Within,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2263)
  - Fielding, Henry, "Jonathan Wild,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2264)
  - Fielding, Henry, "Joseph Andrews,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2265)
  - Fischer, Louis, "Mahatma Gandhi: His Life and Message to the World,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2266)
  - Fjelde, Rolf, Ibsen translations, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2267)
  - Fleming, Ian, general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2268)
  - Fleming, Ian, "Diamonds Are Forever,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2269)
  - Fleming, Ian, "For Your Eyes Only,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2270)
  - Fleming, Ian, "The Spy Who Loved Me,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2271)
  - Foote, I.P., "A Pushkin Verse Reader,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2272)
  - Foote, Shelby, "Shiloh,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2273)
  - Ford, Mrs. E.P., "Real Big Stories,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2274)
  - Ford, Norman R., "The Black, the Grey, and the Gold,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2275)
  - Frame, Donald, "Manon Lescaut,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2276)
  - Franzero, Carlo Maria, "Cleopatra,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2277)
  - Frazer, James George, "The New Golden Bough,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2278)
  - Freemantle, Anne, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2279)
  - Freemantle, Anne, "Anthology of Mao Tse-Tung,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2280)
  - Freemantle, Anne, "Papl Encyclicals,", 1954-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2281)
  - French-English/English-French Dictionary, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2282)
  - Freud, Sigmund, general correspondence, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 2283)
  - Fuller, Robert, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2284)
  - Gaddis, Thomas, "Birdman of Alcatraz,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2285)
  - Gaer, Joseph, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2286)
  - Gaer, Joseph, book on Dunant, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2287)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "The Talmud,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2288)
  - Gaines, William M., "Fighting Mad,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2289)
  - Gaines, William M., "The Mad Frontier,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2290)
  - Gallegos, Romulo, "Dona Barbara,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2291)
  - Gallup, F.H., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2292)
  - Garner, Claud, "Woman in Oil,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2293)
  - Garrett, George, "King of the Mountain,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2294)
  - Garrity, Devin, "The Irish Genius,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2295)
  - Gaster, Theodore, "The New Golden Bough,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2296)
  - Gerlach, Heinrich, "Forsaken Amy,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2297)
  - Gillispie, Charles C., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2298)
  - Gilman, Peter, "Big Sur,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2299)
  - Girodias, Maurice, "Playboy" magazine, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2300)
  - Gissing, George, "The Private Papers of Henry Ryecroft,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2301)
  - Gluckmann, Max, work on social anthropology, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 2302)
  - Gogol, Nikolai, "Dead Souls,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2303)
  - Goldat, ____, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2304)
  - Goldhurst, Richard, "The Deceivers,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2305)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2306)
  - Goldwin,____, and ____ Nelson, "Toward the Liberally Educated Executive,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2307)
  - Goncharov, Ivan, "Oblomov,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2308)
  - Goodman, Dean, untitled novel, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2309)
  - Goodman, Mitchell, "The End of It,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2310)
  - Gordon, Dean Ernest, "Utopia and Anti-Utopia,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2311)
  - Gordon, Noah, nurse novel, 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2312)
  - Gorham, Charles, "The Gold of Their Bodies,", 1955-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2313)
  - Goulet, Robert, "The Violent Season,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2314)
  - Gover, Robert, "The Hundred Dollar Understanding,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2315)
  - Goytisolo, Juan, "L'Ile,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2316)
  - Grant, Michael, "The World of Rome,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2317)
  - Greene, John C., "Darwin and the Modern World View,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2318)
  - Greene, John, "The Death of Adam,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2319)
  - Greene, Joseph, "The Dedicated Few,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2320)
  - Greenman, Longman, "Always Go First Class,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2321)
  - Gresham, William Lindsay, "Limbo Tower,", 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2322)
  - Grey, Harry, "The Hoods,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2323)
  - Griffin, John Howard, "Black Like Me,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2324)
  - Groddeck, Georg, "The Book of the It,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2325)
  - Grombach, John V., "Saga of Sock,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2326)
  - Guerney, Bernard, "Genius of the Russian Theater,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2327)
  - Guss, Jack R., scientist story, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2328)
  - Guttmacher, Alan, "Having a Baby,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2329)
  - Hachette, ____, "Vies Quotidiennes,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2330)
  - Hackett, Marie, "Blind Date With Uncle Sam,", 1960 (Box 79, Folder 2331)
  - Hackett, Paul, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2332)
  - Hackett, Paul, "Erica,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2333)
  - Hackett, Paul, "Obscenity,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2334)
  - Hahn, Emily, "Indo,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2335)
  - Hall, Calvin, "A Primer of Freudian Psychology,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2336)
  - Hall, James B., "Cutlass Bay,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2337)
  - Hamill, Ethel, "Aloha Nurse,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2338)
  - Hamilton, Edith, "The Greek Way to Western Civilization,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2339)
  - Hampton, Kathleen, "The Patch,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2340)
  - Hanawalt, Nelson, "Hamlet,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2341)
  - Hano, Arnold, "Edison Clay,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2342)
  - Hansberry, Lorraine, "A Raisin in the Sun,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2343)
  - Hansen, Harry, "The Civil War,", 1960-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2344)
  - Hardin, Garrett, "Nature and Man's Fate,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2345)
  - Hardy, Thomas, "Jude the Obscure,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2346)
  - Hardy, Thomas, "The Mayor of Casterbridge,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2347)
  - Harkins, William E., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2348)
  - Harnly, Paul W., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2349)
  - Harris, Mark, "Something About a Soldier,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2350)
  - Harris, Sara, "Courthouse,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2351)
  - Hart, Eddie, "Eleven Suspects,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2352)
  - Harvard Business Review books, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2353)
  - Hasek, Jaroslav, "The Good Soldier Schweik,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2354)
  - Hawes, Gene R., "The New American Guide to Colleges,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2355)
  - Hawgood, John, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2356)
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel, "House of Seven Gables,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2357)
  - Haynes, Nora Eddington, "Errol and Me,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2358)
  - Hecht, Ben, "Perfidy,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2359)
  - Heine, Heinrich, anthology, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2360)
  - Heinle, Charles, "Die Geschicte Vom Menschen,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2361)
  - Heinlein, Robert A.., "The Menace From Earth,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2362)
  - Heinlein, Robert A.., "Starship Troopers,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2363)
  - Helseth, Henry E., "The Brothers Brannagan,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2364)
  - Herr, Paul, "Journey Not to End,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2365)
  - Hingley, _____, "Russian: A Beginner's Course,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2366)
  - Hitler, Adolf, "Hitler's Secret Conversations, 1941-44," 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2367)
  - Hittleman, Carl K., "Thirty-Six Hours,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2368)
  - Hodgkin, Thomas, "History of Africa,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2369)
  - Hogan, Ray, "The Life and Death of Clay Allison,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2370)
  - Hogan, Ray, "The Life and Death of Johnny Ringo,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2371)
  - Hogben, Lancelot, "Essential World English,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2372)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, "Elsie Venner,", 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2373)
  - Honig, Edwin, "Cervantes,", 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 2374)
  - Hoopes, Roy H. Jr., "A Report on Fallout in Your Food,", 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2375)
  - Horowitz, Julius, "The Inhabitants,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2376)
  - Horwitz, Stanley, "Mercy Heroes,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2377)
  - Howard, George, "Haste to Succeed,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2378)
  - Hoyle, Fred, "The Nature of the Universe,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2379)
  - Hudiburg, Edward, "Some Loud Night Music,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2380)
  - Huie, William Bradford, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2381)